we know there's no beginning that's help
that's useful yeah
well Sam Austin made it's been a bloody
a bloody pleasure to meet you and I'm
really glad that we're sitting down and
doing this so first of all thank you for
stepping into this space with me thank
you for really appreciate oh yeah it's
it's a strange thing to try and
recalibrate to building a connection
with each other and stepping into some
creative space when there is this
impending adult as probably already set
in a stage a bit negatively with a word
like impending but when there's that
third party an invisible third party in
the room because something that's
characterized all of our interactions
has been it has been almost like that
there has been a safety to step into
that space of real collaborative
expression so how do you feel first of
all about like what does it feel like to
now be sitting here doing this yeah
there's definitely already a kind of
tangible presence almost that is frankly
mind made but I'm very aware of it and
yeah I agree most of our conversations
have been like the framework has been
anything goes essentially and it still
is the case but we're acutely aware that
you know things can be perceived in ways
that we don't actually intend so yeah
yeah that is that is precisely it
there's something about expression that
requires a container that's appropriate
for it which is which is a thread that
I've been working with for a long time
you can think about it in terms of when
do you speak truthfully to for example a
child about a particular experience you
know they do you give them the
the hard dose of truth before there is
some somewhere they can be held when
that truth perhaps overwhelms a
particular conception of the world they
had and so it's sort of like that
there's that to take into account too
and then there's also what of yourself
do you show when you're not precisely
sure who is going to receive that energy
and what will they be doing with it even
to use the word energy is something that
I mean it's it's it's so metaphorical in
some sense that even my using it I'm
conscious that you and I can resonate or
begin to resonate with what we might
mean by that but some listeners might
already be like whoa what energy what's
what's what's going on yeah well I
thought I find it interesting as well
that the energy tends to for me have
more value a lot of the time than the
words do right because the the energy
that's exchanged in the conversation
tends to tell me more about what the
person's really trying to say them what
their words are that sounds pretty
absurd I think when I just said it it
sounds beautiful to me yeah but it
really is in it really does feel like
you can pick up on what I suppose it
comes back to something as abstract as
telepathy in some ways I had a
conversation recently with friends were
where we were exploring that as a
concept and what we've come to realize
is even in the word itself telepathy as
you break it up telly and pathy seems to
have its origins in like telly empathy
and it's more about your feeling the
exchange of the other person's energy
more than your feeling more than your
seeing the words that are inside their
mind you're feeling what they
intend to say mm-hmm and that itself
seems to be a good natural container for
conversations too just to have pure
intentions a lot the time when we're
exploring these more controversial ideas
part of what I really appreciate about
our exchange is that we can entertain
ideas without necessarily being
identified with them and with that
boundary set we can then really dive
into it to explore deeper than where we
let's say authentically app or embodying
at this moment and that would be a
really useful framework itself perhaps
yeah to set it in the beginning of the
podcast like this yeah for the ongoing
progress of voice one right I know I
agree with you the idea being that the
ideas we explore here or not be taken to
be the sort of fixed representations of
yeah yes right however we also have to
cede the expression of those ideas with
a certain sort of intention that has a
purity that can only come from some sort
of authentic manifestation of who we are
which is a strange oppositional thing to
hold as well but before we go too much
deeper this is in some sense we're not
even entirely sure what we're doing here
but for whatever we're doing here it's
important I think that you express to me
but also our audience who you are and
perhaps a little bit about how we came
to know each other and I'd also like to
hear about live learn evolve lle mm-hmm
and what that project has what that
project is and
yeah I'll begin there I don't know yeah
no worries well yeah my name is Sammy
Austin I'm playing the role as live
learn evolve founder mm-hmm which is the
websites live learn evolve calm and it's
essentially a it's a kind of digital
rabbit hole essentially it's a blog but
over the years it's kind of it's evolved
from being like a a site that's focused
on self-improvement from the get-go and
slowly over time has explored various
western philosophies then gone into more
kind of Eastern and esoteric subjects
meditation yoga Buddhism these kind of
psychedelics and kind of culminated now
as an overall digit digital rabbit hole
of content where yeah any of these
topics users can go and dive into mm-hmm
the platform itself and explore it and
find a hole yeah hole yeah hole of
content yeah yeah and it's been a it's
been a natural reflection of my own
journey actually the content itself if
you were to go through the pages of the
site it's very much reflecting exactly
where I am and the other writers and
what I've been resonating with at the
time has been the inspiration to
actually share that on right age right
and so it's been very natural in its
evolution that comes through quite a lot
uh-huh in that from the sometimes we
have a certain conversation and I'll see
something appear on the site you'll
share something huh and it feels as
though yeah that is something that's
something you're grappling with or
battling with that's putting my language
I usually battle with I did maybe you're
a slightly smoother than me but it's if
I could if I could sum up much of the
focus that seems to be put forward its
various pieces of insight
into the process of transformation
mm-hmm that seemed to me to be that way
and I would say it's it's the dance of
transformation that might be one of the
core things that characterizes our
shared interest mm-hmm and the
interesting thing about that is that
that is perhaps the least unique
interest you could actually have and
although expressing it at a certain way
at a certain point of resonance with
someone is necessarily unique as another
one of those oppositional kind of things
and that's and that's another strange
strange tension that has has just come
to be ever more apparent in in my own
experience which is that some of the
most fundamental aspects of life of
experience things you might be tempted
to identify with as special and
meaningful about your life are in fact
over of a source of a shared possibility
that everyone can experience so some of
the most meaningful things in life are
in fact the most fundamental things
there are to do and that can be
expressed in so many ways I mean you
might think about it in terms of shared
stories we all participate in mm-hmm you
might think about it in terms of
archetypes mm-hmm I know we often talk
about have that sort of dance between
the relevance for expression between
sort of form and void or or what is
primary in some sense in how we ought
characterize the state of experience
that might be associated with a kind of
like an emptiness or a no thingness and
then the other side of the coin so to
speak that the grasping of the world
again they're identifying with it again
the contemplating at the fixing it
there seems to be you know that process
itself of releasing from identity and
then grasping it again
is is in some sense an engine of the
most profound nature it's the most
profound thing we do mankind
characterizes us as well as a sort of
like um niche constructors you know as
human beings we're so weakened and you
know everything is a futile when we're
born and it takes us so long to develop
and we have this machinery that enables
us to adapt and so one of the most
fundamental things we are from all these
perspectives is that which transforms
and I we resonate strongly about that so
it is it's bit so it's this like is that
we resonate I resonate but but it's a
but but to resonate involves
relinquishing the I that that resonates
mm-hmm and here we are filming ourselves
it's so strange like it's like always
the coin-flipping ever more ever more
meta and in some sense the absurd point
of view is always there as well you can
you can it's important it's important to
laugh at it mm-hmm so I guess that's a
bit of a riff on transformation but you
think that's a fair characteristic a
fair characterization of of the
transformation and lle and the resonance
that you look to promote yeah for sure
it's definitely been a natural outcome
of that dance of transformation of of
seeking actually myself actually right
and then and then yeah out of that that
which manifests as being as resonating
with me has has then supplied the
inspiration to go and shared up mm-hmm
with an article or a video mhm
or even just on the Facebook page
how do you see your world developing now
like how do you see yourself like wow
it's it's because it's a strange thing
right we we participate in this
interweaving web of society and the
cosmos that is so much larger than us
but is I don't think and I believe you
hold the same view that we can't
consider it separate from us in some
fundamental sense and so we are we are
we are non-dual with it yet we also have
to take on roles at times many roles
throughout our lives perhaps many roles
in the same period of your life with
with different people where we perform
different functions oriented still by
that shared resonance hopefully but the
point is nevertheless we do fix
ourselves in the world for certain
certain purposes and I'm and I'm just
genuinely I'm genuinely interested in
you and I'm genuinely interested in how
you see yourself fitting the world what
role like what feels what feels resonant
to you in terms of concretizing yourself
in it
I don't have I don't put much energy
into the future actually it's kind of
dropped off a lot in terms of if you're
saying about like yet where might I see
this path that you've seen formulating
where it might go I have no idea then
it's actually and I actually have a
preference for that because when I kind
of give up any fixed goal of where it
might go I find that there's a lot more
freedom and whilst it's important that
that I do set goals because I am someone
that's very long conscientiousness yeah
and by actually aiming for them and
being aware that the goals can
dynamically move and adjust as you move
forward a lot of this path has just
being one of surrender it's been a lot
of giving up what I think about the
world mm-hmm and allowing reality itself
to present its symbols and its signpost
for me and then me following that
intuitively in the moment that's really
where there's a lot of freedom so yes
there are a few things on the radar at
the moment for the future where I think
I may focus my attention yeah you know
whether that's like recently becoming
yoga teacher for example which I never
thought I would have done at all right
it was fall off the spectrum but just
using that as an example there were many
many synchronicity synchronicities and
instances whereby the people around me
were out of nowhere suggesting that that
is something that I should pursue
without me even saying anything right
however you do you do have a nature that
I mean they say the feeling I get from
you is authenticity you know and I don't
want to put that too high on it on a
pedestal right like so don't worry I'm
not occasionally you up here or thinking
you do and and what that suggests is
that in fact what is reflected back to
you should those relationships have a
certain degree of honesty towards the
direction of some real reflection
well you'll receive information there
that might help shine the light on
something real for you to realize about
your nature mm-hmm so so so it's
interesting because you know and I find
that very resonant attractive necessary
this attitude towards no fixed outcome
however we also have to have goals and
so there's a combat there is a
conversation to be had about just what
the process of reimagining those goals
are and how all that works but the and
it perhaps would not be right to
formulate showing up in the world as
authentic as itself being an outcome
it's perhaps much
I might say some sort of aligning
yourself with an appropriate expression
or way to be but it but that mode itself
is presenting ice it's like it yeah I
suppose it's it's um it's it's it's
allowing it's allowing yourself to be
realized in a way that it's not solely
relying on its own like it's not a
perverted incestual way of realizing
self mean Jung speaks about
individuation as something that also has
to be carried out in relationship with
others and that idea is resonant with
what we've already begun to articulate
here is a sort of deeper sense of
interconnectedness mm-hmm
so so yeah I don't have a fixed place
I'm really heading with this expression
but that does seem to be a commitment
that the point is that there is a
commitment here to a certain way of
being even if it's not a commitment to a
fixed outcome which I think perhaps yes
important to make conceptually clear
yeah we're definitely um I definitely
say there's been a noticeable shift in
the way I ontologically orient myself in
the world there has been quite profound
and it's it's nothing new at all or
unique to me but it's it's a shift from
attention being focused on the inner
narrative to attention focusing on the
space between the thoughts mm-hmm
it's like a um just a residing in the
space of being through many years of
just surrendering and listening in to
the heart space to the intuition
whatever you want to call it mm-hmm and
then acting from there yes yes I suppose
to the other way around which caused me
a lot of suffering I think it causes a
lot of people suffering yeah
the attachment to that in a narrative
yes a lot the time because it's a
conditioned narrative or yes it's
influenced by external things we don't
have control over and that's that's
brought about a lot of a lot of
inspiration anyway in spirit mm-hmm
it's very mm-hmm I understand I think
that
the articulation of acting from the
place between stimulus and response is a
critical articulation and and learning
in the process practicing the process of
embodying that disposition in your life
is seems to me a necessary a necessary
part of growth and transformation and
ultimately self transcendence it enables
it enables you to actually take the
world in which is which is fundamental
yeah you drop out of being confined to
any particular lens as well
any somewhat towards that way and
perhaps it perhaps its entire taking it
can go as far as entirely being that way
although it's it's had to describe the
place from which there is no lens is in
some respects I mean it that really is
undescribable that is it's a pure it's a
I would say that's a pure well like you
might push back on this and it would be
good and put good to push back because I
said it's a what came to mind would be
to say that's a it's a pure chaos of
experience however it does seem like the
accepting of a place of no lens
transcending that experience therefore
of chaos is something that is attainable
well I tend to see I tend to see the if
your orientation is is primarily focused
on the inner narrative to me that is
chaos and but and the light of awareness
by actually by a perceiving reality by
dropping back into being here in some
ways you'll that is bringing order to
the chaos mm-hmm however however that
does put you in a in a strange position
and I suppose it's always gonna sound
paradoxical when we talk about these
things but it puts you in a place where
where you're standing right now is
facing the unknown mm-hmm because you
you're giving up any ideological lens or
preconceived assumptions or whatever
mm-hmm and you're just facing reality as
it is now and that to some extent could
be can be akin to facing chaos yes yes
now I I understand I would say the idea
of associating chaos with too much
attention paid to the inner narrative is
right but it would seem to me that a
more accurate way of stating it would be
to say well precisely too much
identification with the inner narrative
leads to chaos we it is also helpful to
attend to the inner narrative attending
I think the right word you used there
was identification as well
nice one that
this part is more of an issue than
attending to it yeah right right and
buddy but even then we we take on roles
for certain times mm-hmm so it's so that
so so perhaps a more mature way yet to
refer to what it is to take on an
identity or to attend to it as you
perform it or to perform an identity in
relation with other people in a
situation in the world that that's
something that all be done lightly to
some degree right so so it but but then
I but then I also feel what what comes
to me here is that it's it's worthwhile
to express the importance of well we do
release and while we well it is in an
important sense important to face the
unknown we we're not relinquishing
absolutely everything about what is
helpful to bring with you to navigate
that space it's not I would say about
for example completely abandoning all
lessons of the past you know I wouldn't
say it's about regression although
sometimes perhaps a little bit of fun on
the slightly more immature at or at
least innocent side of things is
necessary so when we're talking then
about stepping into the unknown it's
what is the kit
that that is in fact brought along that
helps navigate the this dance of
transformation is that a question that
is is what I'm saying do you feel me
there do you feel worth articulating
yeah a lot I think what it perhaps comes
down to is like is the importance of
cultivating presence mm-hmm awareness
mm-hmm you know whether that's through a
daily meditation practice or something
where you're dipping into that space
more frequently mm-hmm so that you
familiarize yourself with being lensless
if you want to call it that or just
because in the beginning it's quite
difficult there's this there's a lot of
this whole sections in bookstores
dedicated to mindfulness these days you
know it's it's recognized now as
something that's important although I
find the mindfulness word quite funny is
in be mindful of mm-hmm how fool your
mind is but essentially that's almost
like a westernized version a lot of the
time of what has been primarily
something that the Eastern philosophy
has been so focused on and they're not
so much interested in in being aware of
how before your mind is they're more
interested in clearing the mind right
and that is something that doesn't just
happen instantly for sure there's
there's certainly a practice if we're
talking about our toolkit mm-hmm
we're seeing those toolkits emerge right
now
yoga studios and breath work and
psychedelics these are all ways to help
clear the mind
and yeah it's very it's useful to
mention that because even in the in the
spiritual sphere is there a lot of
people tend to jump on the non-dual
approach of saying well we'll just wake
up now and realize that you're not your
thoughts and be done with it and it's
just a spontaneous thing which can end
now but there seems to be
it seems and that that is actually
normally associated with some spiritual
gurus or spiritual people that are
giving talks or their their running
certain online education programs and
this is all way etcetera and there's
perhaps little set of the relative
aspect of Awakening which is very much
the dance mm between surrendering back
to being and then going back into the
world as the actor and and through that
process cultivating the space of being
so that what you're actually doing is
you're you're informing the mind body
with presence and over time that seems
that allow you to I perceive more
reality as it is mm-hmm
something that came up for me when you
were speaking was that a characteristic
of this cultivation this development of
the experience that persists through
transformation might be something like
the development of the belief in
yourself itself with a big s development
of the belief in your soul an
identification with the very possibility
it's like the transcendent spring of
possibility that enables and is the
precondition for experience at all the
precondition for for joy for force
suffering importantly the precondition
for as well for the transcendence of
suffering and that there is
it's this God something that typifies
typifies my experience and I would
suggest typifies the experience of of
all of us really is this unfortunate
aspect of the dance between connection
and disconnection which is that you can
sometimes feel more disconnected than
you know connected and you know I it's a
the word faith comes to mind here and to
be used like it's it's almost as though
you you you you you cultivate a faith in
your capacity to to remember and come
home again to find connection again
so it's this at one at one thing of
coming of remembering the embo within
the home within even as you face out
into that they'll know yeah yeah and
faith is the the non-rational isn't it
this is the trans rational even yeah
yeah and a lot of the time the reason
that's pointed back as as a surrender
and I often say I'm surrendering
meditation is purely because a lot of
the time the individual is so caught up
and identified with their thoughts the
toolkit they need is to be shown that by
giving up meditation or just
surrendering meditation for a moment is
the way for them to bring more balance
back mm-hmm
because when you do bring balance back
mentation isn't an issue overthinking
necessary because you'll primarily
sitting in the space between you you've
already kind of balanced out mm-hmm it's
like we talked earlier about yeah maybe
it's not the best topic to bring up I'm
gonna free will in determinate like
every denomination not the best but no
just the idea that I would see even in
myself before I went down the the path
of of exploring anything spiritual I
would look back on that as being a very
automated way of living hmm it was
pretty much devoid of freewill in the
way that I look at it now mm-hmm
and that freedom seems to have been
regained by using these tools to
cultivate the space between stimulus and
response right so that now I can clearly
discern what is a habituated action or
patterned thought process mm-hmm
conditioned and what is just pure and
arising as inspiration and intuition and
authenticity as it is mm hmm hmm two
things come to mind one is that due to
the the the grand complexity of life
mm-hmm the complexity that we're
involved in the immense age of the
universe and our biological lineage and
perhaps our metaphysical lineage
the the number of ways to express just
how patterned our existence is is in
surmount it
I wonder if it's truly insurmountable
right like so so the this place of it's
not clear to me that authenticity as
such as means to act from a place where
you are totally attendant to a pure
arising where that's understood as not
being itself just an expression of
another pattern it seems to me more like
the identification with the realization
or the the transcendence of previous
patterns and and sort of like the
voluntary realization of a what more
metaphors kind of a higher frequency and
more maturity mm-hmm deeper sense of
awareness and fitted nurses it's
appropriate for you to walk within a
wider net of of conception of the world
there's more you can appropriately
identify right action in greater domains
larger domains but that the process
itself so I and I think this is
somewhere where we would again resonate
that the process itself of that meets
it's not it it's never-ending
that unlike is it would you say this the
unpacking the the detangling of becoming
who you are would yeah it doesn't seem
to end it would seem that we moved to a
higher process mmm-hmm I say instead
mmm-hmm
but one that is I suppose almost like
biomimicry for some reason that comes to
mind because then the the process of
your action is Springs from nature so
perhaps it's not a mimicry but it's but
by by process by being pure what I mean
is it's it's not conditioned by anything
previous perhaps previously from a minds
conception of what the world ought to be
mm-hmm we would say because it was it's
funny like depends almost what what
perspective you want to take on it it's
like I have no children one day if I am
so fortunate although I can't even hold
on to this too much it would be
beautiful to to raise children I don't
know what that's like and I presume that
there are ways that I can develop so
that I might be able to do that in a
fashion that's more capable than I
perhaps could now mm-hmm
now let's say developing those skills
from the perspective of where we're at
in this conversation one part of that
would be perhaps waking up into an
inherent nature that is there waiting to
be activated so it's it's embedded
within me already to realize and so to
the extent awakening that could be
understood as again this kind of growth
then I am awakening to something that
has a
[Music]
a profound profoundly deep role
narrative pattern of adaptive
functioning in society in the world and
and and so in that sense there is
something in me to be awoken that is
from one angle sort of preconceived it's
like pre it's a it's a there's a seed
that I can't evolve into something it's
the manner in which it evolves and
particular rises it's like it's not just
the seed it's the seed and the ground
and they sort of have to accept each
other and so the dance of transformation
occurs between again seed and ground
agent and arena me and the world in this
case or a family you know in a
relationship or whatever it is so and
and the seed and the ground I mean
another way to also look at it is it's
perhaps the flower blooming when it's
ready mm-hmm you can't kind of force a a
bud to open mm-hmm but perhaps when we
live in this this space of connecting to
where inspiration is behind the
conditioning we're living in a way
that's in line with kind of nature
itself mm-hmm yes we're see where where
there's something in me here okay so
this is this is another place that we
often go to in in the dance we do which
is so so we've been sort of discussing
the the the surrender component the the
relinquishing of narrative and identity
have become fixed in this moment to
align with a novel authentic
re-imagination of how to be in the world
an important part of that process has to
then be okay now we're acting in the
world now we are fixing it again now we
are grasping it again and that to me is
as important as being able to relinquish
or surrender so it's this confrontation
at UC use the terms confrontation and
surrender to sort of articulate
something like this with respect to
navigating psychedelic experience and
look their words and it doesn't really
matter like what matters is the meaning
and there's something about
confrontation that maybe a slightly to
conflictual and so I would say it's this
mixture of it's a it's a cooperative
confrontation of grasping and again it's
about the cycle so whenever you fixate
too much on one you destroy its actual
meaning and its function because they
co-occur but nevertheless we do then we
do fix the world we do grasp it and we
step out and the ego the ego like
bravely steps forward again in its in
its vulnerable and do himself like it's
the price of it is the price of it is
death the price of identity is death but
but the identity itself is to is to be
loved as well you know even though it it
cannot last must be made subservient to
the process of the transformation but
it's it's yeah I I I'm very interested
in what processes in what collective
processes enable this enable the
grasping as well
right it's we have to be doing both
because it you might say a shadow of the
surrender it becomes can tend towards an
apathy to or whatever comes mm-hmm there
maybe that's one of it or maybe there's
a sense of agency that's lost maybe it's
maybe maybe may
surrendering to hey there's a danger of
surrendering at the wrong time might be
manipulation by others potentially so I
don't know how that how that sounds how
that sounds to you there there's so many
different ways to take that I know so I
mean yeah we'll mm yeah generally in the
world at the moment I think it's fair to
say that there's a there's an
overabundance of thinking with a with a
lack of of being so it's more human
doing than it is human being so I think
part of the the solution being
orientated to surrender is perhaps
temporary mmm-hmm
just so that we can restore balance
mm-hmm and there on text matters so
complex eyes matter yeah yeah yeah yeah
it does so in some sense it's like you
and I can talk about perhaps ways to be
with each other things we might do in
the world and it's like it's it's this
is where like things become so like
concretizing messages right and can God
slip so easy into a misinterpretation
and worse still a sort of what engorged
sense of importance and and and
sometimes to commoditization although i
think that's you have to have a slightly
different intent for that as well but
it's like well it's something so strange
about us having this conversation and
and and it being listened to to make
judgments about the world more broadly
because i do agree with you actually i
feel i feel that too at least at least
in the cultures that i've been a part of
and grown up in is that space
of surrendering to the moment is the
capacity to surrender to the moment is
is it is a critical skill but to whether
or not one like it is and over in
indulgence of one or the other like
which way the balance is tipping God
like to very difficult to prescribe very
difficult to prescribe outside of the
actual realization of yourself in
relationship with someone else does that
it's it's tricky it's hard because who
are we who are we speaking we have to
speak about who we speaking to we have
to speak to individuals in some
important it's difficult to me overall
blanket statements I mean I suppose you
could say it's particularly obvious in
the ecological sphere in the way in
which our relationship by the masses is
it's it's disconnected from nature
mm-hmm yes I mean that's very clear
and that seems to be a outer
manifestation of our inner landscapes
I think it's fair it's fair to say that
and the reason why I feel like I can say
that confidently is because I've watched
it in myself for sure and and I've seen
that interplay even down to just the way
I navigate the most mundane experiences
in life like say making a cup of tea
in my daily routine and how much
presence how much attention is paid to
the world and how that is a natural
reflection of
the way I'm navigating things in the
interior landscape mm-hmm but it's also
it's also this space it's it's
connecting with this space that to me is
actually what meaning is it's less that
I've it's less that I find meaning in
particular things as much as meaning
seems to be imbued in direct correlation
to how present I am how how full the
experience of being alive or how how
much a perception there is of just the
felt presence of experience then seems
to imbue whatever is contextually
happening with meaning mm-hmm it becomes
a meaning full and in some ways a lot of
the actions and there's a lot of seeking
I'm seeing in others mm-hmm mm-hmm where
it seems to be what they're seeking for
is what is seeking yes and so rather
than point fingers at X person is doing
this X country is doing this they should
do that etc actually these seem to all
be one problem actually it's not really
a political problem necessary an
ecological problem one of conservative
or liberal etc it's transcending that
it's more of a rampantly untamed ego
that has lost its connection to the
source and yeah perhaps as we say as we
said earlier there's this temporary need
to cultivate that space again to bring
harmony and through that what we should
see is a natural balance with our
relationship to the earth
to each other politically etc it's it's
almost transcends any need for more
information more knowledge it's actually
more wisdom and to some extent wisdom
you know it's more about the embodiment
of knowledge let's say yes then it is
about accumulating thing we're drowning
in knowledge mm-hmm no I think that's
beautifully put I this is uh what I'm
about to do it's it's very selfish but
ah you know good place a good place to
stop there let's check it let's make
sure that was recorded